http://lakelandbank.com/privacy/

Skip to Main ContentAdjust Contrast( Press C )Text Size( Press T )Sitemap( Press S )Accessibility Statement( Press A )Close Toolbar( Press Escape )Need help?866-224-1379 »Secure Email »AccessibilityOptionsSkip to Main ContentAbout UsLocations& ATMsTools & ResourcesOpenan AccountApplyfor a LoanOnline Banking LoginPersonalBusinessFinancial PlanningMortgages
Privacy
Click or Press Enter to Open Menu Online Privacy Statement and Privacy NoticeLakeland Bank (“Lakeland”) is committed to safeguarding information about customers and visitors to this website.Lakeland’s Online Privacy Statement pertains to information that is collected when you visit or transact business on this website. The Privacy Notice explains Lakeland’s policy regarding consumer information applicable to our products and services in general. Consumer visitors and customers using this website may be subject to both the Online Privacy Statement and the Privacy Notice.Online Privacy StatementVisitors to this website remain anonymous. Lakeland may use standard software to collect information about our visitors, such as:Date and time the site was accessedIP address (a numeric address given to servers connected to the Internet)Web browser usedCity, state and countryLakeland uses this information to create summary statistics and to determine the level of interest in information available on the site.Visitors may elect to provide us with personal information via email, online registration forms, or our guest book. This information is used internally, as appropriate, to handle the sender’s request. It is not disseminated or sold to other organizations.Some areas of our website may use “cookies” temporarily stored in the visitor’s computer memory (RAM) to allow the web server to log the pages you use within the site and to know if you have visited the site before.Online AdvertisingIn order for relationship based or behavioral advertising opt-outs from Lakeland sites and other sites to work on your device, your browser must be set to accept cookies. If you delete cookies, buy a new device, access our site or other sites from a different device, login under a different screen name, or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again. If your browser has scripting disabled, you do not need to opt- out, as relationship based or online behavioral advertising technology does not work when scripting is disabled. Please check your browser's security settings to validate whether scripting is active or disabled.Using cookies: Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the device you are using. Cookies we use do not contain or capture unencrypted Personal Information. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the site, pages visited, language preferences, and your relationship with us. We use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, to personalize/customize your experience while visiting the site, and to recognize your device to allow your use of our online products and services. We collect statistical information about the usage of the site in order to continually improve the design and functionality, to monitor responses to our advertisements and content, to understand how account holders and visitors use the site and to assist us with resolving questions regarding the site. We also utilize cookies for our online advertising purposes. Please see the Advertising section below for more information.You can refuse to accept these cookies and most devices and browsers offer their own privacy settings for cookies. You will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser you use. However, if you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the site and some online products and services. For example, we will not be able to recognize your device and you will need to answer a challenge question each time you log on. You also may not receive customized advertising or other offers from us that may be relevant to your interests and needs.Updates to this Privacy NoticeThis Online Privacy Notice is subject to change. Please review it periodically. If we make changes to the Online Privacy Notice, we will update the "Revised" date at the top of this Notice. Any changes to this Notice will become effective when we post the revised Notice on the site. Your use of the site following these changes means that you accept the revised Notice.Online Behavioral AdvertisingLakeland uses advertising service providers to help us determine which of our advertisements are most likely to be of interest to you using certain Other Information such as web pages visited, search keywords entered, or your activities on our site. We limit access and collection of information for specific purposes by advertising service providers.If you prefer we not use relationship based and/or certain Other Information to provide customized content and advertising you have the choice to opt out of remarketing.Opt out of Google’s Ads Settings.Opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.If you don’t want Facebook to show you ads based on your activity on an advertiser’s websites or apps, opt-out here: https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/Print Privacy PolicyRevised February 2019FACTSWHAT DOES LAKELAND BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?Why?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security NumberAccount BalancesCredit HistoryIncomePayment HistoryOverdraft HistoryWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.How?All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Lakeland Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes Lakeland Bank share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes -such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes -to offer our products and services to youYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes –information about your transactions and experiencesYesNoFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes –information about your creditworthinessNoWe don't shareFor our affiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNoWe don't shareQuestions?Call toll-free 866-224-1379 or go to www.lakelandbank.comWho we areWho is providing the notice? Lakeland Bank and its affiliates.What we doHow does Lakeland Bank protect my personal information? To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does Lakeland Bank collect my personal information? We collect your personal information, for example, when you:Open an accountApply for a loanDeposit MoneyUse your credit or debit cardPay your billsWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.Why can't I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only:Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthinessAffiliates from using your information to market to youSharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.DefinitionsAffiliates Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.Our affiliates include Lakeland Preferred Equity, Inc., and Lakeland Financial Services Agency, Inc.Nonaffiliates Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial or nonfinancial companies.Lakeland Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.Joint Marketing A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products and services to you.Our joint marketing partners include a credit card company.Navigation: Rates, Contact Us, Careers, Security, Privacy and SitemapHomeRatesContact UsCareersSecurityPrivacySitemap866-224-1379FacebookInstagramLinkedInBlogYouTubeRouting Number: #021205376Equal Housing LenderFDICSBA Preferred Lender©2020 Lakeland Bank - All Rights Reserved.
